今日本报头条
According to today's newspaper headlines
汽车节目主持人
it seems that it's the end of the road
杰里米 克拉克森的职业生涯要告一段落...
for motoring presenter Jeremy Clarkson...
...很遗憾
...and said that it's with deep regret
高层决定 对他不予以复职
the decision had been taken not to renew him.
预计今日天气晴朗
forecast plenty of sunshine through today
正常季节温度
with seasonal temperatures.
午间气温可能高达28摄氏度...
We should reach a high of about 82 degrees by this afternoon...
*我能清楚看到大雨已过*
*我能清楚看到未来障碍*
*蒙蔽双眼的阴霾已散尽*
*光明马上就要到来*
*阳光灿烂的日子*
*伤痛过后 我深信我定能成功*
*不好的情绪也已消失*
*祈祷的彩虹就在眼前*
*光明和阳光*
*将洒满这天*
*伤痛过后 我们奔向成功*
*不好的情绪都已消失*
*我能清楚看到大雨已过*
*这将是阳光灿烂的一天*
*将是阳光灿烂的一天*
*光明和灿烂*
*将洒满这天*
*带走这些阴霾吧*
*阳光灿烂的一天*
大家好
Hello, everybody!
翻译
17 Mo OckRAZOR
掌声送给温室花朵乐队
Hello. That was the Hothouse Flowers.
翻译
lxbenz 小老虎 shan natas
现在我们看到这位
And now, look what we have here.
翻译
小小C oliver monica-卡
他生于-
He was born-
他生于1836年...
He was born in 1836...
校对
natas Geoff 17 OckRAZOR 幽蓝心晴 RN
他曾让 汽车杂志 给炒鱿鱼了
He was fired by Car magazine
时间轴
木南 肉肉 natas RN
让 机动车 杂志炒了
fired by Autocar magazine
让 苏格兰周日报 炒了
fired by Scotland On Sunday
而且
and somehow
他还能让沃尔沃经销商给炒了
he managed to get fired by a Volvo dealership.
有条件的朋友可一定要去亚马逊支持正版哟
谢谢
Thank you.
可能就是因为开车太慢
Probably for driving too slowly.
各位 詹姆士 梅
Ladies and gentlemen, James May!
谢谢大家 你们太热情了
Thank you, thank you. You're very kind.
好的 女士们先生们
And, ladies and gentlemen
接下来这位 后排的观众可能看不见他
you probably can't see him from the back
但是我保证 他在台上
but I assure you he is here.
他曾被约克电台给炒了
He was fired by Radio York
被利兹电台炒了
fired by Radio Leeds
被兰开夏电台炒了
and fired by Radio Lancashire
这位就是 理查德 哈蒙德!
it's Richard Hammond!
大家好 谢谢你们的热情
Hello! Hello! Thank you!
谢谢
Thank you.
女士们先生们
And, ladies and gentlemen!
这位
Over here!
他 他基本上
He's- He's basically
是一只剃了毛的猿 穿着人类的衬衫
a shaved ape in a shirt.
严格意义上 他也是我们中唯一一个
And he, technically, is the only one of us
从未被任何公司炒过鱿鱼的人
never to be fired by anyone.
掌声欢迎杰里米 克拉克森
It's Jeremy Clarkson!
谢谢大家
Thank you so much.
好消息是
And the good thing is
我现在不太可能被炒鱿鱼了
it's very unlikely I'm going to be fired now
因为我们这是网络节目
because we're on the Internet
这意味着 节目里我能和马快活快活了
which means I could pleasure a horse
不行不行不行
No! No No
-狗呢 -不
-Dog? -No.
严禁各种快活
No pleasuring of any sort.
-这是全家一起看的节目  -好吧
- There are families watching. - Yes!
说回正题 我们都是汽车记者
Anyway, we are all car journalists.
在过去20年间...
And we have spent the last 20 years...
-我们一直在被炒鱿鱼  -可不是吗
- Being fired. - Yes.
但是我们已经将毕生所学
But we have poured everything we know
和所关心的一切投入这个节目
everything we care about, into this show
倾尽所有 接下来的短片
Everything. And coming up now is a small montage
包含了未来12周你们要期待的所有精彩
of what you can expect over the next 12 weeks.
准备好了吗 两位
Are we ready, gentlemen?
讲真 我也不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
夭寿
Argh!
这是坡太抖还是他的命根子出事了
Is that the size of the drop or what's happened to his penis?
你现在看到的东西叫壮观
You're looking at magnificence.
救命 大事不好
Help! This is bad.
詹姆士说我们得停下来加油
James says we've got to stop for fuel.
我恨你!
I hate you!
他不喜欢我们呢
He doesn't like us.
我的天
Bloody Nora!
好像有点轻微漏水
May be leaking slightly.
傻犊子
What a moron.
你玩坏了我的豪华轿车
You sunk my limousine!
我鼻子里的卫生棉掉了一个
I've lost one of my nose tampons.
这不是一件很文明的事
This is not a particularly cultural thing to do.
我不喜欢晚上烧胎的味道
I don't like the smell of tire smoke in the evening.
赶紧回来
Oi! Get back in!
詹姆士要掉下去了...
James is falling...
穿亚麻西装漂移
Sideways in linen.
这事很伤自尊 对吧
There's no dignity in that, is there?
对
No.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you so much.
听我说 谢谢
Now- Thank you.
我们将在这里给大家呈现以上所有内容
All of that is gonna be hosted from this.
这是我们新的移动演播帐篷
This is our new travelling studio tent.
非常感谢 我们将在这里面环游世界
Thank you so much. We're gonna be roaming the world in it.
就像吉普赛人一样
We're gonna be like gypsies.
不同的是我们开的车都会上保险
Only the cars we drive are gonna be insured.
不要再说这种害我们被炒掉的话了
Stop saying things that are gonna get us fired.
我只想说这太棒了
But I'm just saying, it's brilliant.
真的
It is.
喂 谁把我们的无人机打下来了
Oi! Who shot our drone?
-有人开枪了吗 -是他
- Did someone shoot it? - Him.
先不纠结这些了 好吗
Let's not get bogged down in who shot what, okay?
咱们把衣服换了然后继续主持节目吧
Let's get changed and get on with the show.
我们该继续吗
Shall we get on with the show?
好的 来吧
Let's do it.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everybody!
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
欢迎来到史上第一期GT的现场
And welcome to the first ever Grand Tour.
谢谢 希望你们喜欢这个帐篷
Thank you. Now, we hope you like our tent.
我们觉得最棒的是 因为我们会带着它周游世界
We think the great thing is that because it roams around the world,
所以每周窗外的景色都不一样
we get a different view out of the big picture windows every week.
比如这周 很明显外面
So this week, obviously we've got
是加州的莫哈维沙漠
the high desert of California.
-下周是哪里 没人知道  -我知道
- Next week, who knows? - I do.
废话 詹姆斯 我们当然知道 是约翰内斯堡
Well, yes, James, we know. It's Johannesburg.
-现在他们都知道了  -我知道 但是无所谓
- Now they know. - I know they know! It doesn't matter!
重要的是景色每周都变 观众也如此
The point is the view changes and so does the audience, okay?
这周你们都是美国人
This week you're all Americans.
现在有这么一个小问题
Now, this is a bit of a problem
对于我们这些说英语的人
for people like us who speak English.
在商店餐厅这些地方交流都没问题
We can converse perfectly well in a shop or a restaurant,
但当说到汽车与驾驶的时候
but when it comes to cars and motoring,
你们和我们用的词都不一样
every single word you use is different.
我的意思是你们说的都是错的
When I say "different", I mean "wrong."
那根用来换挡的杆子你们叫什么
When you change gear with a lever, what do you call that?
- Stick  - Stick
- Stick. - Stick.
看好了 这才是Stick
Now, you see, this is a stick.
没法用这个换挡
Couldn't change gear with this.
不过倒是可以用来指指东西
Wouldn't work. What you can do with this is point at things.
我来给你们上一课
Let's see if we can get you educated.
车的这部分你们叫什么
What do you call this bit of a car?
- The Hood  - Bonnet
- The hood! - Bonnet.
hood又是帽衫的意思
- Bonnet - 他们在学习
- Bonnet. - They're learning.
你说什么 我当然知道不能把Bonnet戴头上
What do you mean? I know you can wear a bonnet on your head.
两种意思 我们是能够理解事物有两种意思的
It's two things. We're capable of having those different thoughts.
-这种车你们叫什么  -Pick-up
- What type of vehicle is this? Pick -up.
不是的 这种车叫蠢
No, it's stupid.
-等等  -真的很蠢
- Oh, now, hang on. - It is stupid.
再来个类似的
Let's do another one of these.
-这是什么车型  -Coupe
- What type of vehicle is this? Coupe.
Coupe吗 Coop是用来养鸡的
Coupe? Coop is where you keep your chickens.
coop与coupe美语相近 coop 农业合作社
这叫Coupé 我承认这是个法语词
That's a coupé. That's a French word, I admit.
- 是的  - 但他们把这个都搞混了
- Yeah, a bit. - They're muddled with that.
你们知道乔治布什曾经说过什么吗 有关法国人
George Bush, have you heard what he once said about the French?
他说 法国人的问题就在于 他们没有
"The trouble with the French is they have no word
能够用来形容entrepreneur的词
for entrepreneur."
entrepreneur：法语词，企业家
确实很难 我认为只有一个词是我们都认同的
It is difficult. I think the only thing we agree on
- 方向盘 - 是的
- is "steering wheel." - Yeah.
但他们又把方向盘的位置放反了
But then they go and put it on the wrong side of the car.
一直这样开车一定挺麻烦的
It must be really annoying having to drive along like that all the time.
就不能像我们一样 把方向盘放到驾驶员面前吗
Why don't you just put it in front of the driver like we do?
我觉得我们还是继续节目吧
It's probably a good idea if we get on with the actual show.
好主意 但要先澄清一下
Yes, it is. But we had to clear all that up,
和某些人的说法不同
because contrary to what some people have been saying,
这确实是一档汽车节目
this actually is a car show.
-但下周不是  -下周是个特例
- Well, not next week it isn't. - Next week is an exception.
-是的  -我们去巴巴多斯那期也不是
- Yeah. - But not when we go to Barbados either.
没错 巴巴多斯绝对也是一个特例
No, Barbados is definitely another exception.
但今晚绝对是一档纯正的汽车节目
But tonight couldn't be more "car-y" if it tried.
我会证明的 因为今天要以它开场
I'm gonna prove that point because we're kicking off with this.
等一下 等我说完
Bear with me, bear with me-
我同意
I agree!
我想说的是
The thing is, though,
现在许多超级跑车制造商采用了
various supercar makers have now taken
和普锐斯相同的保护生态环境技术
the polar-bear-friendly technology from a Prius,
只不过是用来创造原始 野蛮的速度
and they are now using it to create raw, naked speed.
我觉得在所有这些混动究极跑车中 最棒的是
Now, I say the best of these hybrid hypercars
那辆疯狂的 斜着眼睛的迈凯伦P1
is the mad, swivel-eyed McLaren P1.
而理查德 哈蒙德错误地认为
Whereas Richard Hammond, who's wrong-
我没错
I'm not wrong.
他错误地认为最棒的是
He is, because he says the best
那辆无聊的保时捷918
is actually the rather boring Porsche 918.
-一点也不无聊  -无聊
- It's not boring! - Yes, it is.
-不无聊  -真的
- It isn't. - Mm-hmm.
好吧 随你怎么说
It isn't. Well, whatever.
我们决定开着这两辆车碰个头
We decided to meet up with the cars
然后终结这场争论
and settle this once and for all.
这场史诗对决的地点选在了葡萄牙
The location we chose for this titanic duel was Portugal...
再具体点就是在阿尔加维赛道
specifically, the international race track of the Algarve.
我们刚到 保时捷和迈凯伦的技术人员
When we arrived, mechanics from Porsche
就立刻扑向了我们的车
and McLaren pounced on our cars,
为接下来的对决做准备
fettling them for what was to come.
这也意味着哈蒙德和我有时间
And this meant Hammond and I had some time to indulge
来做一些幼稚的评头论足
in a spot of childish point scoring.
哪辆车在这个赛道上是最快的
Which one of these is going to be the fastest around this track?
-这辆吗  -是的
- This? - Yeah.
除了这辆 哪辆更快
Apart from this one, which will be faster.
不可能 你认为哪辆车最快
It won't. Which one do you think will be the fastest?
-这辆  -这辆
- This one. - This one.
所以两边都觉得自己的车最快
Porsche think the Porsche will be fastest. McLaren say the McLaren.
如果我要买的话这车多少钱
How much is it if I wanted to buy one?
我记得有一辆被拍卖到了180万
I think one was sold in an auction for 1.8 million.
180万美元 哈蒙德 你的多少钱
1.8 million dollars. Hammond, how much is yours?
838欧元
838 euros.
-单位是千吗  -是的
- Thousand I'm guessing? - Yes. It is thousands.
为什么你的车门上有个数字
Why has your car got a number on the side?
这是Weissach特别版
It's the Weissach edition, this one.
-它还配有钛合金底盘螺栓 -太蠢了
- You also get titanium chassis bolts. - Stupid.
只需要多花上6万英镑
For just an extra ?60.000.
还有个碳纤维引擎盖支架
And a carbon-fiber bonnet strut.
看看 能省出多少重量来着
Look at that. How much does that save?
-大概100克  -不错吧 100克呢
- About 100 grams. - Right there, 100 grams.
迈凯伦有没有碳纤维引擎盖支架
Has the McLaren got a carbon-fiber bonnet strut?
-我们不需要 -我不需要支起引擎盖
- Doesn't need one. - No, because my bonnet doesn't go up
因为它永远不会抛锚
because it will never break down.
而且它还有两扇呆门 正常门 呆门
And it's got silly doors. Proper doors, silly doors.
我的百公里油耗只有8.3升
Mine does 34 miles to the gallon.
我只有3升
This does 94.
-百公里才3升吗  -3升
- 94 miles to the gallon? - 94mpg.
提醒我一下 保时捷的母公司是
Just remind me, Porsche is owned by?
大众
That'll be Volkswagen.
指大众排放门事件
很快这两辆车都已准备好下赛道了
Soon the McLaren and the Porsche were ready for some shakedown laps.
我们决定先开一开对方的车
And for these we decided we'd drive each other's cars.
一上来我就能告诉你
Straight away, I can tell you
这辆车没有迈凯伦的
that this doesn't have the brutality or the savagery
那种残暴和野蛮
of the McLaren.
因为它有后轮转向和四轮驱动
Because it has rear-wheel steering and four-wheel drive,
让人感觉很放心和安全
it feels secure and safe.
而这也会给你信心
And that gives you the confidence-
让你自由发挥
...to play about.
如果我用迈凯伦以这个速度过这个弯
If I went round this corner this fast in the McLaren...
会有很多翔跑出来的
...a lot of poo would come out.
已经有翔跑出来了
Whoa! There's poo coming out now!
天啊
Jesus.
轮胎在六档还特么的打滑
It's spinning its wheels in sixth!
这车太吓人了
This is frightening, that's what it is.
哇 更多的翔
Whoa! More poo.
我从没想到一个人会因吓出的翔太多而死
I didn't think it was possible to shit yourself to death.
抓地力实在是太棒了
The grip is genuinely incredible.
这才对嘛
Oh, there you go.
在这辆残暴而无情的P1里
In the savage and unforgiving P1,
我脆弱的神经都碎成了渣渣
my nerves were shot to pieces.
但也深深地爱上了它
But I, too, was falling in love.
903匹马力
903 horsepower.
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
你这个淘气的坏家伙
Oh, you bad, bad, naughty car!
天呐
Jesus.
这辆车会刷新你的认知
This recalibrates your mind.
我本以为没有车能像918那样充满激情
I didn't think anything could be as exciting as that Porsche,
但是它做到了
but this- this is.
这辆车太棒了
This is brilliant.
真的太棒了
Absolutely brilliant.
噢
Oh.
一辆神奇的车
What a car.
我太爱它了
I love it.
-怎么样  -真是辆破车
- Well? - This is rubbish!
巧了 我也是这么想的
I was just thinking exactly the same about this.
-是吗  -它无聊到让我想死
- Were you? - This was boring me to death.
像维多利亚时期的女性小说一样无聊
It was like being stuck in a Victorian woman's novel.
总比和一只发疯的猩猩被困在一个电话亭里强
I'd rather that than being stuck in a telephone box with a panicking gorilla.
- 破车  - 它想杀了我
- Rubbish.- It was trying to kill me.
- 它一直想害死我  - 我就喜欢这点
- It wants to hurt me.- That's why I like it.
这辆车就好比传教士体位
This is a missionary-position car.
外科医生手中的刀片
Razor blade in the hands of a surgeon.
醉酒农民手中的镰刀
Sickle in the hands of a drunk peasant.
唐顿庄园 绝命毒师 那是冰毒
Downton Abbey. Breaking Bad. That's crystal meth.
这是一捆大麻
That's some iffy weed.
一瓶上等红酒 一箱纽卡索啤酒
Fine wine. Crate of Newcy Brown.
大杯雪莉酒 苦艾酒
Schooner of sherry. Absinthe.
詹姆斯邦德吩咐
James Bond specifying
马天尼是用摇的而不能搅
his martini to be shaken not stirred.
猜火车里的贝格比
Begbie in Trainspotting
在夜店把啤酒杯抛过自己的肩膀
lobbing a pint pot over his shoulder in a night club
然后干一架 咋了
and starting a bar fight. What?
你们好呀
Hi.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
二位 我来是因为
I'm here because, gentlemen,
在我卡车的后面有一辆
I have in the back of that lorry
使你们的迈凯伦和保时捷
something that will make your McLaren and your Porsche
看起来相形见绌的车
look like lumps of yesteryear.
我想不起来上次一辆车
I cannot remember the last time a car,
或者其他任何东西
or, indeed, any sort of thing,
像拉法一样让我如此兴奋了
gave me a fizz like the Ferrari LaFerrari.
这辆车有950匹马力
This has 950 horsepower.
950匹啊
950.
马力比其他两辆都大
More than either of the other two.
而且还更轻 只有1250公斤
And it's lighter. It weighs 1.250 kilograms.
这比大部分掀背车都轻
Which is less than most hatchbacks.
实际上拉法的本事还不止于此
Actually there is a bit more to the Ferrari LaFerrari,
因为它配备了F1的KERS系统
because what it has is, in effect, a formula one KERS system.
能够随时通过电机和电池
It constantly recovers energy that would otherwise be lost
回收原本会被浪费的能量
using its electric motor and its battery.
所以当我踩下刹车的时候
So as I brake there,
车子其实在说 这些能量我全要了
the car is actually saying, "That energy, I'll have that."
大直道
Straight!
这才是950匹马力应有的感觉
This is what 950 horsepower feels like!
天呐
Jesus!
我相信它能够碾碎那两辆车
This I believe will absolutely mince the other two.
这速度
Oh, man!
詹姆斯显然在鬼扯
James was obviously talking nonsense.
但毫无疑问的是
But there's no getting around the fact
这三台车将汽车科技
that these three cars take automotive science
带入了新纪元
to a new level.
它们运用最新的环保技术
They use the latest green technology
从每滴燃油中
to squeeze as much speed as possible
压榨出更多速度
from every molecule of fuel.
结果便是 它们都有能力
As a result, they're all capable of blasting
在极速超过 320Km/h 的同时
way past 200 miles an hour
排出比家用车还少的有害物质
whilst producing fewer harmful emissions than a family saloon.
这是三台令人难以置信的机器
What we have here, then, are three incredible machines
它们的横空出世
which, at a stroke,
使传统的超级跑车显得
have made the traditional supercar look wooden...
既简陋又落后
and old-fashioned.
各位 欢迎来到三神车的世界
Welcome, everyone, to the hypercar holy trinity.
左后视镜里是价值100万英镑的保时捷
In that door mirror I have a one million Porsche.
右后视镜里是价值100万英镑的法拉利
In that door mirror I have a one million Ferrari.
今天真是玩过瘾了
What a toy box today.
大猩猩的屁股冒出了火花
Sparks from Jezzer.
你干不掉我的 哈蒙德
I don't think so, Hammond.
这应该相当昂贵
This could be so expensive.
我要提速了
It's going to boost.
按下 IPAS
Pushing the IPAS button!
我额外获得了170匹马力
And that gives me another 170 horsepower.
启动 DRS
Opening DRS!
噢我的天啊
Oh, my Christ!
太快了
Bloody...
开着拉法的梅来了
And here comes May in the Ferrari LaFerrari.
集中精神 不要分心
Concentrating. Concentrating.
噢吼 那辆该死的车
Oh-oh! That bloody car
我不在里面的时候也想搞死我
is trying to kill me, and I'm not even in it.
哈哈
Ha-ha!
我们本可这样玩一整天
We could have played out there all day,
但在一场价值300万英镑的车祸发生之前
but before we ended up in a three million pound crash,
我们决定还是先开始测试
we decided to start the tests
看看谁的车才是最好的
to see which of the cars was best.
我想出了第一个测试
I came up with the first one,
主要是为了欺负梅这个不速之客
mainly to annoy gate-crasher May.
咱们的第一个测试是直线加速赛
Let's make the first test a drag race
-但只能用电能 -好主意
- using electrical power only. - Good idea.
-才不是呢  -为什么
- It isn't a good idea. - Why not?
因为拉法不能用纯电驱动
Because you can't drive the Ferrari on electrical power only.
-不是吧  -当然不能了
- No! - Of course you can't,
因为它用的是类似F1的KERS系统
because it's a KERS system like a Formula One car.
有一台V12引擎和一个电动机
It's got a V12 engine and an electric motor,
但二者是集成的 只能同时工作
but they are integrated, they work together, you can't separate them.
-你早就该想到的 不是吗  -大意了吧
- You should have thought about that, shouldn't you? - Bad planning.
把詹姆斯贬为旁观者之后
With James reduced to the role of onlooker,
我俩把P1和918摆到了起点
we lined up the P1 and the 918 on the start line,
但我们并没有轰油门
but then, instead of revving the petrol engines,
而是关掉发动机
we shut them down.
太诡异了
That is weird.
在一片寂静中准备
Preparing to start a drag race
开始一场直线加速赛
in complete silence.
我现在仍然拥有两个电动机
I still have two electric motors
总共能产生285匹的马力
that together produce 285 brake horsepower
比他那辆迈凯伦
which is 109 more
上面的单电机要多了109匹 噢耶
than the one electric motor in his McLaren. Oh, yeah.
我先走一步
I'm outta here!
你一定会喜欢电动机
You've got to love that, the immediate power
这种直接的动力输出
from an electrical engine.
现在时速已经超过110公里了 但还是不够快
That is 70 miles an hour already and it isn't enough.
刚才谁赢了 是我吗
Who won that? It was me, wasn't it?
是你赢了 但这并不重要
Yeah, but it's not important though, is it?
-真的不重要吗  -并没有什么意义
- Is it not? - It's just not relevant.
好吧 好吧
Right, right.
直线加速赛的意义就是看谁先通过终点
In a drag race, it's irrelevant which car gets there first?
没错 你这辆更适合当送奶车
Yeah, yours is the better milk float.
回到P房 哈蒙德想出了下一个测试
Back in the pits, Hammond had an idea for the next test.
我们要开车去酒店 离这里大概有一个小时
We've got to drive to the hotel yet. It's about an hour away.
正好给了我们一个机会 看看它们在公路上的表现
It gives us a chance to see what they're like on the road.
-很有道理  -回到现实世界
- That's a good point. - Real world.
-点子不错  -我做不到
- That is a good point. - I can't do that.
我不能把拉法开上路
I can't drive the Ferrari on the road.
-为什么  -这辆车还没注册
- Why? - It's not registered.
不是啊 上面还挂着牌照呢
It is, it's got number plates.
不 那只是个假的牌照
No, that's just pretend number plates.
如果注册了的话 这辆车就变成二手车了
If they register it, it becomes second-hand
还要交税 所以我才用卡车运过来
and they pay tax. That's why it came in the lorry.
所以你也不能把它开上路
So you can't drive it on the road either?
谁也不行 上路是非法的
Nobody can drive it. It's not road legal.
-噢 不  -兄弟 真扫兴
- Oh, no. - Mate, that's...
-太遗憾了  -你要开一个小时的
- That is such a shame. - It's an hour of-
你今天真是太不走运了
That's really a rotten bit of luck.
从意大利千里遥遥地开过来
'Cause you've come a long way from Italy.
我也不能带你一程
I can't give you a lift
因为录音师的设备都在副驾座位上
'cause the soundman's headphones are on the seat and the mixer.
太惨了
Oh, no.
我真的无能为力了
There's literally nothing I can do.
不久之后 理查德和我便开始享受
Soon Richard and I were enjoying
世界上最美妙的一段旅程了
the world's best-ever commute.
内饰看起来可能有些粗犷
It may be a bit Spartan in here,
但开起来却出人意料地舒适
but it's unbelievably comfortable.
因为它的防倾杆
Because it uses electronics
已经电子化了
rather than traditional anti-roll bars.
也就是说车轮之间
That means there's no physical connection
没有机械上的连接
between the wheels.
所以当一个车轮遇到颠簸的时候 其他车轮不会受到影响
So if one goes over a bump the others aren't affected.
太不可思议了 就像在开劳斯莱斯幻影
It's uncanny. It's like being in a Rolls-Royce Phantom.
美妙的傍晚 把顶棚拆下来
It's a lovely evening. Taken the roof panels out.
空调开到合适的温度
Set the air-con just so.
享受在这乡间开车的感觉
And I'm enjoying a drive in the country.
与此同时
Meanwhile...
我勒个擦
Oh, bloody hell.
倒 倒 倒
You're all right.
意大利语的 倒 倒 倒
You're all right, in Italian.
天啊
Oh, God.
-詹姆斯 -干啥
- James. - What?
抱歉我必须要说 法拉利太没用了
I'm sorry to have to say this, but that Ferrari is useless.
好好好 一会第二节
Yes, yes, yes. Later on in part two,
这哥俩终于放弃那些
when these two have stopped dreaming up
我没法参加 又毫不相关的
idiotic and irrelevant tests
愚蠢测试 我们再见分晓
that it can't take part in, we shall see.
行行行 这个环节里
Fair enough. Now,
我们仨坐下聊聊
at this point in the show we like to sit down
新车和汽车行业的那些事
and chew the fat about new cars and motoring issues.
比如 凭啥英国要在修路期间限速80
Like, for example, why in Britain we have to drive at 50 miles an hour
然而并没有人在干活
when they're doing roadworks to protect the workforce which is never there.
好吧好吧
Yes, okay...
而且为啥那些成熟的成年人
And why fully-grown adults
要骑着儿童玩具在城市穿梭呢
have taken to riding around the city on children's toys?
-是 没错-我觉得那叫自行车
- Yes, okay. - I think they're called bicycles.
-这词没错吧-并不是那样的问题
- Is that the right word? - It's issues like that.
这个环节叫做唠嗑街
It's a segment we are calling Conversation Street.
-额-咋了
- Well... - What?
我们可是在这视频里下了很多功夫
We put a lot of work into that!
这个真是非常非常难做
It was really, really hard doing that.
更赞的是 我们很到位地
Better than that, rather brilliantly, we have made
给接下来每集的这个环节
a bespoke version of that sting
都定制了个片头
for every single episode
接下来三年里 每集都不一样
we're gonna make for the next three years.
怎么样
How about that?
打断一下 这里有个小问题
But hold on. The slight problem with that
我们之前一直忙着做这片头
is that we were so busy doing that
以至于没想过这个环节里到底唠什么
we didn't think actually of anything to talk about.
-我们想过啊-是啊
- We did. - Yeah.
-啥-你们肯定喜欢
- What? - You'll love this.
詹姆斯 梅 世界上移动速度最慢的人类
James May, the world's slowest moving human being,
居然被抓到超速
has been caught speeding.
真的被警方罚款
Actually charged by the police.
罪犯
Criminal.
其实他对这事挺自豪的
He's actually quite proud of it.
他当时骑着本田CBR 600RR摩托
He did it on a Honda CBR 600RR sports bike.
事实上...
The thing was...
理查德和我大吃一惊
Richard and I were genuinely astonished.
他跑到办公室来说
He came into the office and said,
我超速被抓了
"I've been done for speeding."
直到我们发现他到底开多快
Until we found out how fast he was going.
詹姆斯 当时开多快
James, how fast was it again?
59公里时速
37 miles an hour.
狂人 真是牛逼
Crazy! Mad man!
那么快的速度 你是怎么呼吸的
How did you even breathe at that kind of speed?
警察怎么抓到你的 用腿跑吗
How did the police catch you? Were they running?
肯定是慢跑追上你的
Gentle jog for sure.
要是你也被抓过超速
The thing is, if you've been caught,
我们真不信这世上还有人会这样
'cause we genuinely don't believe anyone in the world has,
如果你曾被小于59的时速抓超速
but if you've been caught speeding at a speed less than 37,
请写信告诉我们
do honestly please write to us and let us know.
因为我们实在是觉得不太可能
'Cause we don't think it's possible.
在你的信封写上 我是乌龟
And mark your envelope, "I'm a tortoise."
这就是本期唠嗑街
And that is all we have time for this week
的全部内容
on Conversation Street.
-等等等等-干啥
- Whoa! Hang on a minute. - What?
这可是第一集 你们俩上来
The first-ever show, and you just mock me
嘲笑一下我的罚单就结束了
for my speeding ticket and then we move on?
这节目时间很紧的
It's a busy show.
时间那么紧 我们得向观众介绍我们的赛道
It is a busy show. We've got to tell everyone about our track.
嗯 我们真有赛道的
Yes, we have one.
这是个你要在街上
This is the sort of place where you can drive cars
也这么开车的话
at speeds that you can do on the road
就会被扔进监狱的地方
but only if you want to go to prison afterwards.
比如开到60
What, like 38 miles an hour?
甚至61 62这样
39 maybe even, 40 from time to time.
本来呢 我们打算着
Now, we were hoping that we could bring it
把赛道和帐篷一起打包带走
round the world with us like the tent.
但可惜 它太沉了
But unfortunately it's too heavy,
而且如你即将所见 特别爱咬人
and, as you are about to see, too bitey.
就是这个
This is it.
这不是赛道
It's not a race circuit.
也不是机场
It's not an airfield.
也不是公路
It's not a road.
它是出色和速度的结合体
What it is is brilliant and fast.
并且及其危险
And extremely dangerous.
地图上看着也危险
It even looks dangerous on a map.
因为你看 这形状跟埃博拉病毒
Because as you can see, it's the exact same shape
一模一样
as the Ebola virus.
现在就带你们看看这赛道什么样
Right, time now to show you what a lap looks like.
为了这 我们选了性能标杆
To do that we've got a bit of a performance benchmark.
法拉利488
A Ferrari 488.
走你
Take it away.
你倒是走啊
首先是 不直道
First up, it's the Isn't Straight,
因为它真的不直
so called because it isn't straight.
极速左弯紧随一个极速右弯
There is a super-fast left followed by a super-fast right.
如果你犯错 这可没有缓冲区或防护挡板
And if you make a mistake, there's no run-off area or Armco.
直接就进树林了
It's just woods.
全是野生动物
Woods that are full of wildlife
喜欢朝你冲过来
which likes to run out in front of you.
过了不直道的第二个右弯
After the second right on the Isn't Straight,
我们就来到了留你名弯
we're into Your Name Here Corner.
各种赞助冠名机会在此
Sponsorship opportunities are available here.
但是我得说明一下
However, I should explain
可能没人会看你的条幅
that it's possible nobody will be looking at your banner
因为这个弯被设计成让车来做...
because this is a corner that was designed
...这事的
so a car can do this.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
詹姆斯 梅 今天并没有来
James May... isn't here today.
这个只是我一个朋友
That's just a friend of mine
在他回到不直道之后...
on his way back up the Isn't Straight...
就到了外婆家弯
towards Old Lady's House.
我们把这叫外婆家
We've called this section Old Lady's House,
就是因为这旁边有个房子
because it's right next to a house
住着一个老奶奶
where an old lady lives.
她跟我们说她喜欢车
She tells us she likes cars.
她说她之前有一辆车
Says she used to have one.
不太确定她在我们这么折腾之后
Not sure she's going to like them quite so much
还会不会喜欢车了
after we've been here a few times.
紧接着就是一个狭窄颠簸的冲刺
Next up, there's a narrow and bumpy sprint
直到变电箱
to Sub Station.
你得处理好这个90度左弯
You need to get this 90-left right,
不然你就栽进全是电的笼子里
or you'll crash into a cage full of electricity.
最后一个90度左弯也得如此
And you'll need to get the final 90-left right as well,
不然就会冲进羊群里
or you'll run into a field of sheep.
那么 树啊 小动物啊
So, trees, animals,
房子啊 电啊
a house, electricity,
而且还是在英国
and because it's in England,
空气一直都很潮
usually quite a lot of moisture in the air.
这真是世界上最危险的赛道
It really is the most dangerous track anywhere in the world.
为了能在这个赛道留下你的记录
To post a fast time here,
你真的要
you do need...
那些
those.
我选择下埃博拉症赛道的车
The car I've selected for my first lap
就是这个
of the Eboladrome is this.
宝马M2
The BMW M2.
遗憾的是 在我们第一集节目里
Sadly, there isn't the time in this, our first-ever show,
没时间做公路测评了
to do a full road test of this car,
不过我倒是有时间说
but there is time to say that I think
我觉得这是宝马有史以来最棒的M
this is the best M car BMW has ever made.
这年头很多性能车
In a lot of fast cars these days,
都装了各种旋钮 按钮
you get all sorts of knobs and buttons
用来改变-
which you can use to change-
我说改变 其实是毁了
I say change- I mean ruin
引擎 悬挂
the characteristics of the engine
和转向等的个性
and the suspension and the steering and so on.
我一直觉得 这就像个厨子
And I always think, isn't that like a chef
把鱼给你端上桌
bringing a fish to your table
然后放上烤炉 黄油 一点西芹
and an oven and some butter and a bit of parsley,
然后说 你自己做吧 才不要啊
and saying, "Cook it yourself"? No.
你来烧啊 我花钱就为了这个
You cook it, it's what I'm paying for.
可喜的是 这辆车
This car, happily, has a more
更回归本质一些
back-to-basics approach.
M2里面 下面有个小开关
In the M2 you get a little rocker switch down here
完全没有用
which does nothing at all
就我来看 就这么多
as far as I can see, and that's it.
你所买到的车在出厂前
You're buying a car which was set up at the factory
就由那些知道自己该干嘛的工程师设置好了一切
by engineers who know what they're doing.
而你要做的就是好好享受驾驶乐趣
And all you have to do is enjoy it.
就像我现在这样
Which I am doing.
爽啊 看看这个
Yes, look at this.
太喜欢这个了
Oh, yeah, loving that.
我要再做一次 来验证-
I'll do that again, actually, and make sure-
来验证我是对的
make sure I was correct.
几乎就没有什么转向不足
There's hardly any understeer at all.
尾巴甩出去 保持住
Poke the back out and hold it there.
耶
Yeah!
再来一次
I'll do that again...
反过来
only going the other way.
开留你名弯
Wrong way round Your Name Here.
克劳斯和弗瑞茨 我爱你们的作品
Klaus and Fritz, I am loving your work.
哎呀 我搞砸了 但我只要这样
Oh, I made a mess of that. But I'll just do this,
就能让一切看起来像是故意的
and it'll look like I did it on purpose.
随着轮胎不停求饶
With the tires begging for mercy,
我来到了不直道
I got back onto the Isn't
然后把这3.0升直6双涡轮发动机的
and unleashed 365 rampaging horsepowers
365马力狂暴的释放了出来
from the turbo-charged three-liter straight six.
跟M3比 这车直路并不快
This isn't as fast in a straight line
不过除此之外一切...
as an M3, but everywhere else...
都更棒
it is better.
感觉更轻 更灵活
It feels less heavy, less cumbersome.
而且我们这个直道的特性
And due to the unique characteristics of our straight,
我能感觉到转向没那么
I can tell the steering is less...
焦躁
It's less twitchy.
这个赛道就是为了刁难车的
This track was designed to trip cars up.
这里有极速弯
There are fast corners,
慢速弯
slow corners,
漂移弯 还有颠簸
drifty corners, and bumps.
对轮胎
It's hard on the tires.
刹车 引擎都有着极大的考验
It's hard on the brakes. It's hard on the engine.
危机四伏 让你尖叫
It's point and squirt and bark and yelp.
极其凶狠
It is vicious.
但这些都无法难倒M2
But there is nothing here which has flummoxed the M2.
这绝对是惊世之作
This thing is an absolute masterpiece.
像我说的 这是宝马造过
Like I said, it is the best M car
最棒的一辆M了
BMW has ever made.
你可能会觉得我疯了
You may think it's mad to suggest
认为最便宜的M是最好的
the cheapest M car is the best,
但要这样看
but look at it this way,
这个赛道比银石赛道便宜很多
this track is a lot cheaper than Silverstone.
我却知道我已心有所属
And I know which one I'd rather drive round.
去开开M2吧 令人难以置信
Go drive an M2. Unbelievable.
怎么了
What?
老奶奶家那里怎么有连续弯
Why is there that zigzag at Old Lady's House?
我去时不是这样啊 -对 那时是的
- That wasn't there when I went. - No, that wasn't.
但是你走了之后 我们发现
But after you'd left, we discovered there is
那有一颗没爆的二战炸弹 讲真
an unexploded Second World War bomb, seriously,
就在赛道的位置 所以要绕开它
right where the track was, so we had to go round it.
有道理 -我总结下
- Fair enough. - Let me get this right.
在我们的赛道上 有树 动物
At our track, there's trees, animals,
湿气 电气设备
moisture, electricity,
一栋房子 和一个没爆的炸弹
a house, and an unexploded bomb?
没错 像我说的 这是世界上最危险的赛道
Yeah. Like I said, it's the most dangerous track in the world.
讲真 它让伊莫拉变得像过家家一样
Honestly, it makes Imola look like a duvet. Honestly.
不管怎样 我们在埃博拉症赛道测的每一辆车
Anyway, all the cars that we test at the Eboladrome
都会跑一个计时圈
will do a timed lap.
为了确保条件公平
And to make sure it's a completely level playing field,
它们都会由同一位车手驾驶
they will all be driven by the same racing driver.
哦
Ooh!
我们想到这点了 我们动过脑子了
We thought about this. We gave it some thought.
我们多机智  现在
How clever is that? Now...
问题是 亚马逊坚持
The thing is, Amazon insisted
我们要选的车手
that the racing driver in question
必须是大洋这边的人
should be from this side of the pond.
所以我们去了一个叫纳斯卡的地方
So we went to something called NASCAR?
找了一个 把他运到英国
And we found one. We shipped him to England
然后教给他一套复杂的动作
and then we introduced him to the complicated procedure
其中包括 向右转弯
which involves turning right.
他叫麦克 斯吉那
He's called Mike Skinner,
但我们只管他叫 老美
but we know him simply as "the American."
需要提醒你的是
We should warn you
他有些观点十分强硬
that some of his views are quite strong.
是的 他的观点非常明确 比如
Yes, he has very specific views, for example,
气缸数少于8个的车
on cars that have engines with fewer than eight cylinders.
-我党 -或多于8缸的车
- Communist. - Or more than eight cylinders.
-我党 -发动机在中间的车
- Communist. - Or cars that have their engine in the middle.
我党
Communist.
一切非美式V8的都是我党
Everything that isn't American really with a V8 is communist.
所以让我们看看他和M2相处如何
So let's see how he gets on with the M2.
他就在这了
There he is.
不知所措 东张西望
Looking utterly bewildered.
但是他出发了 稍稍打滑
But he's off. A skitter of a wheel spin.
立马进入不直道
And immediately he's onto the Isn't Straight.
这有个让他困扰的右弯
There is a right there that will have confused him.
接着左弯 他应该很擅长
Now a left, he'll be good at that.
可以油门全开了
Now he can open the taps.
3.0升 6缸
Three liters, six cylinders.
这东西连狗屁股里的油绳
This thing wouldn't pull a greasy string
都拔不出来
out of a dog's ass.
我完全不明白他在说什么
I've literally no idea what he's talking about.
在我的家乡 这不是一辆车
Where I come from, this ain't a car.
这是求助的哭喊
It's a cry for help.
管他吧
Whatever.
开过了不直道的最后一个弯
He's through the final corner on the Isn't Straight.
进入留你名弯 大力刹车
Into Your Name Here. Hard on the brakes.
紧握换挡杆
Grabbing the stick,
当然挡杆现在在他左边了
which is on the left-hand side of where he's sitting,
然后入弯
and turning in.
看到没 完全没有转向不足
See what I mean? No understeer at all.
这破赛道比我家的车道还窄
Damn tracks are narrower than my driveway.
那是因为你家车道上停着台怪物卡车
Yeah, that's 'cause it doesn't have a monster truck on it.
真想知道谁把这玩意搞出来的
Wonder which one of them came up with this thing.
那个高个子 小矮子 还是留着娘娘腔头发的
The tall one? The short one? Or the one with the girly hair?
好的 到了外婆家弯
Okay, coming up to Old Lady's House.
大脚刹车
Hard on the brakes.
转过弯 绕过没爆的炸弹
Turning in, round the unexploded bomb,
又可以冲刺了
and now opening the taps again.
完全没有涡轮迟滞
No turbo lag at all,
冲过了颠簸的小直道
as he hammers down the bumpy back straight
前往配电站
towards Sub Station.
这是个直角弯
This is a 90-left,
新铺的柏油 但抓地力不错
new Tarmac but it held it well.
绵羊坡上还有个直角弯
One more 90-left to go through Field Of Sheep.
漂亮的过弯 冲线
And he's done it well. And across the line.
处女秀 真的很不错
First one. That's good.
他很优秀
He's great.
他既会左转也会右转 真厉害
He's great going left and right. Amazing.
为了避免这辆M2
To make sure that the M2-
在圈速榜上孤单一人
that wasn't on the lap board all by itself,
我们把这个美国人扔进了其他标杆车里
we got the American to put other benchmark cars-
我们叫标杆车型 他叫我党车型
we call them benchmark cars, he calls them communist-
来跑几圈 看看他们到底几斤几两
around the track, to see what's what.
有迈凯伦 奥迪 等等
McLaren, Audi and so forth.
等下 我在之前片子里
Hang on a minute. We saw a Ferrari 488
看到了法拉利488
at the track in the film earlier on.
为什么它没上榜
Why isn't that on there?
因为法拉利不让我们测圈速
Because Ferrari wouldn't let us time it.
-不让测  -不让
- Wouldn't let us? - No.
所以说 法拉利拉法不能上路
So the Ferrari LaFerrari can't go on the road
-没有纯电模式 -是的
- or run on electric only? - No.
然后488还不能来测圈速
And the 488 can't do a timed lap?
法拉利那边总是很难交涉
Ferrari are quite tricky to deal with from time to time.
我们别去管他了 来看看
Let's just put it that way and move on. It's time to see
M2在榜上能排在哪
where the M2 goes on that board.
拭目以待 把圈速放上来
Let's have a look. Let's put it on.
-噢 -哈哈
- Oh! - Ha-ha!
哇 哇
Wow! Wow!
我觉得这是他们造过最好的M
"I think it's the best M car they've ever made."
这可不是我说的
Not my words.
虽然这车最慢 我却独钟情于它
"I prefer it to all the others that are quicker than it."
-是 但这只是 -这车是最佳选择
- Yes, it's- - The one you should have,
如果你想要一辆最慢的M系的话
if you want one that's slower than all the other M cars.
没这么惨 仅仅慢了两秒-
It's better. It's only two seconds-
-至少比思域快 -确实
- It's quicker than a Civic. - Yeah.
但它还是慢过
But it's slower than-
如果你把M车型列出来 选一辆车
If you had a choice of M cars, lined them up,
然后说 我想要最快的 那绝对不是这辆了
and said, "I'd like the fastest", it wouldn't be that one.
-闭嘴 -在每一点上都更好
- Shut up. - Better in every single way?
-那是你说的 -我不管 你开过M2吗
- You said that. - I don't care. Have you driven one?
-开过-简直是惊世骇俗
- I have. - It's fabulous.
这真是辆好车 真的是
It's a brilliant car. It really honestly is.
可惜 我们不能带着赛道环游世界
It's a shame we can't take the track round the world with us.
真要这样 我们就能邀请明星来开
Because if we did, we could invite celebrities to drive round it
还能弄个圈速榜
and we could keep a score sheet
看看谁最快
of who was the fastest.
我不喜欢这主意
No, I don't like it!
我也不喜欢
I don't like it, no.
我不信它能火啊 -没人爱看这个
- I don't think it would work. - Nobody wants to watch that.
真不信 不管怎么样 我有更好的主意
I'm not sure that they do. Anyway, we've got a better idea,
我们的明星环节
Okay, for our celebrities.
就叫它 明星脑碰脑
We're calling it Celebrity Brain Crash,
我们也做了个小片头
and we had a sting made for that as well.
太糟糕了
That is terrible.
我不想用这个
I don't like to use this...
实在太糟了
It's just terrible.
谁会说 我要去看亚马逊的新汽车节目
Who is gonna say, "I'm gonna watch that new Amazon car show.
里面亨利八世的脑袋炸了
Henry VIII's head explodes"?
为什么布拉德皮特的头在冒烟
Why is there smoke coming out of Brad Pitt's head?
这是想表达什么
What are we trying to say?
不 我们不是 -我们不是这意思
- No, we're not. - No, we're not saying that.
不是这个意思
Not that.
这个片头糟透了
That is a terrible sting,
但这仪器真不错
but the machine itself isn't terrible at all.
这是用来测量人体灵活度
It's used to measure somebody's mental agility,
观测能力
their observational skills
以及多线程操作能力
and their ability to multi-task.
实际上它是基于
It's actually based on a machine
给要加入皇家空军
that's used to test fighter pilots
战斗机飞行员测试的仪器
who want to join the Royal Air Force
我们都知道 这是全世界
which, as we all know, is the finest and greatest air force
最好的空军了
in the world.
你们这喝倒彩什么意思
What do you mean, "Boo"? What do you mean, "Boo"? What?
要是这样 你们每次出状况为什么还要我们帮忙
If that was true, we wouldn't have to help you every time you get in trouble.
我先坐下忍着
I'll hold myself back here.
等等 你们怎么抱怨都行
Now, hold on. You lot can grumble as much as you like,
反正这节目是由我们英国人来剪辑
but we edit this show and we're British,
所以这肯定会被切的
so you'll just get cut out.
我们都同意
We're all in agreement.
皇家空军就是比美国空军好
That the Royal Air Force is better than the US Air Force.
美利坚 美利坚 美利坚
USA! USA! USA!
我们都同意
We're all in agreement
皇家空军就是比美国空军好
the Royal Air Force is better than all the other air forces in the world.
我们现在都同意
We're all now in agreement.
皇家空军是
The Royal Air Force is-
世界上最棒的
is the best air force in the world.
我们都同意 皇家空军还是比较厉害的
So we're all in agreement the Royal Air Force is quite good.
差不多就行了
That will do. That will do.
我们回到明星脑碰脑
So let's get back to Celebrity Brain Crash
看看我们第一位嘉宾
and meet our first-ever guest.
在其他节目里
Normally on other shows,
嘉宾一般都会从亮闪闪的幕布里走出
the guest will come through a sparkly curtain,
挥手致意 然后坐下 这里不一样
wave a bit and then sit down, but not here.
没错 我们的嘉宾入场可正式了
Oh, yes, our guests make a proper arrival.
这样 有请今晚的嘉宾
And on that note, let's meet tonight's star.
他几乎参演了所有的
He has been in pretty much
大型系列电影
every single movie franchise there is
除了单身日记
apart from Bridget Jones.
他就是主演啊
No, he was Bridget Jones.
是么 -不
- Was he? - No.
不过没关系 他参演过谍影重重
But it doesn't matter. He was in the Bourne films.
还演过碟中谍
He was in the Mission Impossible films,
还有复仇者联盟
the Avengers films,
现在 他在我们头顶3000米的高空盘旋
and right now he is 10.000 feet above us,
等着进行华丽的入场
waiting to make one hell of an entrance.
女士们先生们 杰瑞米 雷纳
Ladies and gentlemen, Jeremy Renner!
他在那 就这架飞机
There he is. There he is, that's his plane.
他来了
Hold on, everybody. Here he comes.
他准备跳了
He is ready to jump.
准备好了
I'm ready!
他准备跳了 他来了
He is ready to jump. And there he goes!
能看他自己做特技
That is amazing
简直神奇啊
to see him doing his own stunts.
没错 而且他看上去真帅
Yeah, I know. And he is looking good!
等他到了
When he gets here,
我想和他聊聊谍影重重4
I do want to talk to him about that Bourne Legacy film.
一是 揍肖恩 雅克博森什么感觉
what it was like to punch Shane Jacobson.
二是 等等
And, B... Ooh, hang on.
他开伞好晚啊
He's leaving this terribly late.
好吧
Right.
这是不是就意味着他来不了了
Does that mean he's not coming on, then?
是的 詹姆斯 他来不了了
No, James, he's not.
没关系 我们已经预料到有类似的情况了
It's okay, though. We anticipated this sort of thing,
我们有一个替补嘉宾
so we got a back-up guest ready.
额
Uh...
他出演过秘密特工
He was in Man From Uncle.
出演过独行侠
He was in Lone Ranger. He was both twins
在社交网络里同时扮演了双胞胎
in The Social Network.
他最新出演的电影叫做夜行动物
And his new film is called Nocturnal Animals.
很抱歉我们没有时间
We haven't had time, unfortunately,
来安排一个戏剧性的入场
to organize a dramatic entrance,
但我希望各位还是欢迎他的到来
but I hope you'll give him a warm welcome nevertheless.
女士们先生们 有请 艾米 汉莫
Ladies and gentlemen, Armie Hammer!
他那里
There he is.
哦 我的
Oh, my...
天啊
Jesus!
那是一条蛇么
Is that a snake?
是的— 是条响尾蛇
- It's a snake. - That's a rattlesnake.
真的— 是啊
- Is it? - Yeah.
他在垂死挣扎 各位 请安静
He's being killed. Quiet, everyone.
请安静一下
Quiet, please.
我们真的什么都做不了
There's literally nothing we can do.
他离我们好远啊
He's yards away from us.
但毒蛇是一群一群的
Snakes are like herds of them.
他们群体打猎 -他们是群居动物
- They hunt in packs. - Yeah, they're pack animals.
这是不是说 他也进不来了
Does that mean he's not coming on either?
是的 詹姆斯 他在痛苦的抽搐中死去
No, James, he's finished writhing around in agony.
现在他死翘翘了
And now he's dead.
所以他也进不来了
So that is a no.
好吧 额
Well, uh...
也许我们的观众里有一些名人呢
maybe there's somebody famous in the audience.
不太可能吧
That's unlikely.
怎么不可能 你们知道 卡罗尔·沃德曼 么
No. Seriously, you know Carol Vorderman?
她今早给我打电话说她在附近看航展
She rang me this morning from an air show nearby
还问能不能来参加节目
and said, can she come to the show?
我知道你们不知道卡罗尔 沃德曼是谁
I know you don't know who Carol Vorderman is.
她在英国可是红得发紫啊
She's a huge, huge, huge star in the UK.
她从一档叫做Countdown的节目里发迹
She started out on a program called Countdown
在剧中 将自己打造成无比聪慧
and established herself as being unbelievably brilliant,
美轮美奂的数学家
a fantastic mathematician
此外还漂亮
and very beautiful.
是呢  她也死了
Yes, she's also dead.
嘛
What?
啥 -她死了
- What? - She's dead.
这是什么情况啊 -不知道 我又不学病理的
- How did that happen? - I don't know. I'm not a pathologist!
但是她像这样就死了
But she's dead is what she is.
真的么 -是啊
- Seriously? - Yes!
天啊 -出事了吧
- Christ. - Problem.
我们现在应该怎么办呢
What are we gonna do?
额
Um...
天啊 看看这外面 就像个
Jesus, look at that out there. It's like a-
简直横尸遍野啊
It's just littered with corpses.
弟兄们 我觉得这环节没有存在必要了
Lads, I don't think this bit is working.
我们就把
Let's drop
明星脑碰脑 这周的给切了吧
Celebrity Brain Crash this week.
下周去了南非再搞
We'll do it again in South Africa next week,
等下周 大家就把这事给忘了
and I think people will have forgotten all this.
不会吧 -我觉得他们会的
- They might not. - I think they will.
我们把这段跳过去吧 这些事情从来没发生过对吧
We'll just skip over it now. It's not gonna happen.
好吧 因为我们要回到车上来
That's okay, 'cause we can back to the cars.
是的 继续
Yes! Moving on!
别看 -对 别看
- Don't look. - Yes, don't look.
这周呢
This week-
这周我们要在新世代混动超跑中找出
This week we are trying to find out
他们中哪台是最好的
which of the new breed of hybrid hypercars is the best.
是的 第一天我们在葡萄牙赛道上
Yes. On day one at the track in Portugal,
我们发现迈凯伦P1是一个神经质
we established that the McLaren P1 is a mentalist,
保时捷918是个不错的送奶车
that the Porsche 918 is a very good milk float,
法拉利拉法什么都干不了
and that the Ferrari LaFerrari can do nothing at all.
有些话是真的
Some of that is true.
但是 现在是第二天
But now, day two.
我们将寰宇中最热血澎湃的
We began by lining up
三辆速度机器依次排开
the three most exciting cars on the planet
准备进行这个时代的巅峰之战
for the drag race of all drag races.
自然而然 这就意味着要打开弹射起步了
Naturally, this meant engaging launch control,
在迈凯伦里 大约需要2周
which in the McLaren takes about a fortnight.
我要把驾驶模式调节到赛道模式
I have to have the drive tray in track mode,
空气动力学模块调节到运动
the aero package in sport mode,
在这个模式下 车辆后部会降低
so that the rear end squats
当我起步的时候回给我更多的抓地力
when I set off and gives me more traction.
我还需要将DRS按钮用我的大拇指按住
I have to have the DRS button pressed with my thumb
让尾翼变得水平以极大减小迎面的空气阻力
to keep the rear wing open which reduces drag obviously.
在保时捷里开弹射 左脚踩刹车 猛踩
Launch control in the Porsche, left foot on the brake hard.
右脚踩油门 猛踩
Right foot on the throttle hard.
绿灯一亮 左脚一抬 叮
Light goes green, left foot off brake. Pa-ching!
持续按住弹射起步按钮2秒钟
Launch button, press for two seconds.
左脚踩刹车 右脚踩油门
Left foot on brake. Right foot on throttle.
按下弹射起步 狠踩油门
Press launch control, mash the throttle,
四秒内松开刹车
within four seconds release the brake.
三秒钟后 我将达到最大增压值
Three seconds later, I have full boost,
并且在三秒钟内我必须起步
and I have to set off within three seconds
否则的话整个系统将取消弹射状态
or the entire system disengages.
我肯定会失败的
I'm going to get this wrong.
通知你们一下
Just so you know.
我的准备工作太多了
I've got a lot to do in here.
我没准备好
I wasn't ready.
天啊 那辆拉法真快
Oh, my God! That is quick!
亲娘啊 看到了么
Holy mother! Did you see that?
我* 天啊
- me! - Jesus Christ!
到处乱窜
It's all over the place.
既然大家都心知肚明是我按错了按钮
Since it was clear I'd got all my buttons wrong,
伙计们也都同意再赛一轮
the chaps agreed to another run.
情况报告 增压还没好
Sit rep, the lights went green
灯就变绿了
before the boost was ready,
我还按住了DRS按钮
and I had the DRS button still pressed
所以到最后 我没了下压力
when I got to the end, which meant I had no downforce,
结果就是 吓出了翔了
which meant- Well, poo came out.
这次 我要加大下压力
This time I'm gonna do it with more drag,
虽然会慢些 但是刹车的时候
which will slow me down, but I will be able to stop
我才没有生命危险
without killing myself.
KERS系统充电完成
KERS system charged. Right.
增压中
Boost building.
3 2
Three, two...
出发了 神起步啊
And we are away! What a start!
保时捷后来居上了
The Porsche has got off to a flyer.
啊 我的蛋
Oh, balls!
180 190 200 210
180, 190, 210.
230公里每小时
230 kilometers an hour.
这没发挥好
That wasn't very good.
因为詹姆斯不知怎么搞砸了
Because James had somehow messed up that time,
而且这测试的重点在车
and because this test was about the cars,
所以我们决定再来一次
we decided to go again.
这就是个火箭
It's a rocket ship.
为了大英帝国
For England!
不要啊
No, no!
我们都赢过一次了
Okay, we have all three won this now.
为了最终确定
Determined to find a definitive
一二三的排名
one-two-three finishing order,
我们又跑了一次
we ran again.
两位 这又是一个完全不同的结果
Another totally different result there, gentlemen.
又一次
And again.
又是个不同的结果
That's a different result again.
又一次
And again?
至此 我们决定
At this point, we decided to call
不再继续下去了
a halt to proceedings,
因为我们得出了一个科学结论
because we had reached a scientific conclusion.
原来这和你买哪辆没关系
It turns out it doesn't really matter which car you buy,
主要是鞋的问题
it all depends on your shoes.
大家看 这是一双TOD乐福鞋
Now, this is a TOD loafer.
轻微的磨损 能够让起步的瞬间
Slightly worn to get a crisper jump
松刹车的动作更加干脆直接
off the brake pedal, and it's immediate.
他的是匡威 鞋底的填充物比我想象还厚
- This is a Converse. - There's more sponge in there than I thought.
你看阿迪也是 他们造鞋的时候也没考虑过这个问题
See, Adidas, they weren't thinking that through.
所以在你抬脚的时候就已经损失了一毫秒
- So, as you lift your foot up- - It's a millisecond.
无论是你有KERS
I know you've got KERS,
你有6.3升V12引擎
I know you've got a 6.3-litre V12,
还有出色的弹射启动
and I know that launch control system is amazing,
最终都被
but it's all let down
你的阿迪达斯鞋给耽误了
by the sponginess of the Adidas shoe.
所以车和鞋应该配套卖
So they should sell you the car and the shoes.
不止 首先你得有合适的鞋 然后还要磨合一段时间
No, have you got the correct shoes and have you worn them in?
没错 新鞋的话 不好意思各位
- Exactly. - Fresh shoes, lads.
我需要 你需要磨一下才行
- I just need to- - You need to skid about. There we go.
解决了这个问题之后
With that sorted,
就该请出我们的职业赛车手
it was time to bring in a racing driver
来试试哪辆车的圈速最快
to see which of our cars could do the fastest lap.
我们的常驻美国佬表示对此不感兴趣
Our resident American said he wasn't interested,
因为这三辆车党性太足
because all three cars are probably communist.
所以我们找了一个比利时佬
So instead, we went for a Belgian chap-
曾跑过一级方程式和E级方程式
...who's done Formula One and Formula E,
他就是Jerome d'Ambrosio
Jerome d'Ambrosio.
为了了解每辆车的操控特性
Jerome took the cars out
Jerome进行了试驾
to get a sense of how they handled.
在他完成之后
And when he'd finished,
我们都想听听
we were interested to hear
专业人士的意见
his professional opinion.
让我们从保时捷说起
上帝啊 我告诉你 这是个死亡陷阱 到处乱窜
它运行最顺滑 车子性能很中性 因此风险也很大
像是在和头油腻的猪摔跤 别再让我开了
非常好的牵引力 驾驶感觉十分舒适 我对它很信任
好吧 是这样的
的确
这台法拉利真是一辆漂亮的车
这台法拉利 糟糕的车
弯道表现太混乱了
有着很好的平衡性
在这三车里 法拉利是最均衡的
三辆车里 它绝对是最差
买这车的 肯定是精神病院出来的
这辆车十分迅速 我对它有很大的信心
是的 是挺差劲
说起迈凯伦 它无疑是杰作
迈凯伦 也许是最难以控制的
容易驾驶 如行走的诗般美妙
这真是野蛮的车 因此很容易犯错误
实话 孩子都能开
需要时刻当心 很难协调
因此我认为它不太有效
蹒跚学步的小孩
后来我们才知道
At this point, word reached us that Jeremy
这段的字幕是杰里米自己瞎配的
was taking liberties with the subtitling machine.
所以继续我们的壮举
So we moved on to the big event:
计时赛
the timed laps.
一旦技术人员完成了准备工作
Once the mechanics had finished their preparations,
这三个测速点就会被激活
the three speed traps were activated.
法拉利拉法 在起跑线上
And the Ferrari LaFerrari took its place
找到了它的位置
on the start line.
看它多漂亮啊
Look how good it looks there.
这只是浪费时间 浪费橡胶和汽油
This is just wasting time. It's wasting rubber and fuel.
不 这就像是开胃小点
No, this is like an amuse-bouche.
是啊 明明已经点了鸭子和雪莉蛋糕
Yeah, it is. You have ordered the duck and sherry trifle.
-你拿了个蜜瓜球 -我听都没有在听
- And you're a melon ball. - I'm not even listening.
西餐常用小蜜瓜球装饰开胃小点
伙计们 它现在时速231.4公里
Gentlemen, it is doing 231.4 kilometers an hour
在直线的尾端
at the end of the straight.
差不多柴油版高尔夫之类的速度
It's about the same speed as a Golf diesel, something like that.
194.9.
利用重力一路下坡
Going down the hill using gravity.
他停下来去购物了 他肯定的
- Is he stopping off for shopping? - He must be.
他来了
Here he is.
-詹姆斯 边上风凉去吧 -反正车手热过身了
- James, if you want to get a cup of tea. - We've warmed the track.
下面 该轮到保时捷918出场了
Next it was the turn of the Porsche 918.
这些条纹会给它的速度加持多少呢
How much faster will it go because of the stripes?
很多
Much.
231点多
231 point...
所以他比法拉利快
So he's faster than the Ferrari.
183.0.
比他慢了非常多
Way, way, way slower than him.
别忘了在这里和下一个测量点之间
Don't forget between here and the next measuring point,
好的 你还有四个慢速弯道
Okay, you've got four slow corners,
这些就是保时捷将要赶超上来的地方
and those are the ones where the Porsche is gonna make up time.
因为四轮驱动
Because of the four-wheel steering.
像本田披露一样 -不
- Like a Honda Prelude? - No!
110点什么 1
- 110 point what? - One.
所以 比你快了 0.1
So, almost to a tenth of a kilometer an hour, the same speed as you.
他来了 他这暴躁的声音
Here he comes. He's firing noises.
在这里 快看那个
There it is. Look at that.
终于 是精神病人杀手出马了
Finally, it was the turn of the psycho killer.
这三个中最难搞的 最易怒的
The trickiest, the edgiest of the three.
但是我对它会胜利充满了信心
But I was so confident it'd win,
所以我准备豪赌一把
I was prepared to take a massive gamble.
如果迈凯伦是最快的
If the McLaren isn't the fastest,
你们两个可以把我的房子拆了
you two can knock my house down.
-神马 -把它拆了
- What? - Knock it down.
-你的房子 -是的 就是这个意思
- What, your house? - Yeah, and I mean that.
这就是我有多坚定的认为它将会是最快的一个
That's how confident I am that that will be the fastest.
-你知道我们真的干得出来的 -是的
- You know we will do that? - Yeah.
-这是个严肃的打赌 -是的
- It's a serious bet? - Yeah.
-好的 -如果它不是最快的
- Fine. - If that's not the fastest,
-我们可以把你的房子拆了 -对哒
- we can knock your house down? - Yup.
你们知道它在哪里 你们都去过
You know where it is. You've both been.
我很愿意把它拆掉
I'd love to knock it down.
我们开始吧 这影响很大
Here we go. A lot riding on this.
235.9.
好的 它在第一个直线的末端是最快的
Okay, it's fastest at the end of the first straight.
你们愿意来我的家共进晚餐吗
Would you like to come to my house for dinner?
好啊 我能带个推土机一起来吗
Yes. Can I bring a bulldozer?
188.3.
这真是令人心惊的快啊 -利落
That is worryingly quick. Brisk.
这还是挺快的吧
It's quite brisk?
我们还不知道它急转弯的时候可以开多快呢
We don't know how fast it's going around the tight turns.
也许在那里它只能做到两公里
Might have been doing two kilometers an hour around here.
他在哪里
Where is he?
撞车了
Crashed.
随着这个 让我们回到帐篷
With that, back to the tent.
谢谢你们 现在
Thank you so much. Now...
我要把话说清楚
I want to make it absolutely plain,
因为这对一些怪胎们很重要
'cause I know this matters to anoraks,
所有的这三辆车用的都是完全一样的轮胎
all three cars were running on exactly the same sort of tires.
是的 一样的轮胎 一样的赛道 一样的车手
Yes, same tires, same track, same driver.
所以时间只和车本身相关
So the times are down to the cars.
是的 而现在是揭晓答案的时候了
Yup. And now it is time to reveal those times.
让我再说清楚一点
Let me just make it absolutely clear.
我们并不知道这些时间
We don't know what they are.
制作人一直瞒着我们
The producers have kept them from us.
这是顶级机密 -是的
- They're top secret. - Yup.
所以 让我们打开记分板
So, let's put the scoreboard up,
让我们从
and let's begin with
法拉利拉法开始
the Ferrari LaFerrari, I believe.
让我们来看看它做的如何 拜托
Let's see what it did it in, please.
我们并不知道这究竟好不好 不是吗
We don't know if that's any good, do we?
接下来让我们看看保时捷
Let's move on and do the Porsche next.
保时捷到底开了多快呢
What did the Porsche do it in?
啊万岁 1:54.2
Oh, yes! 1:54.2!
耶 耶 你看到了吗
Yes! Yes! You see?
你说它会把保时捷碾压成渣
You said it would mince the Porsche.
但是它并没有 它比保时捷慢
And it didn't mince it. It was slower than the Porsche.
我告诉你了它华而不实
I told you it's just a melon ball.
它比我的车慢
It's slower than my car,
换种说法比你的车快
which was faster than your car.
0.2秒而已 而且它看上去更好
0.2 of a second, and it looks better.
是 在我后视镜里 还越变越小
Yeah, it did in my mirror where it belongs getting smaller.
它就是华而不实 它输了
It's a melon ball, and it lost.
-哈蒙德 -干嘛
- Hammond. - What?
-冷静下来 -好吧
- Calm down. - All right.
因为接下来
Because now we must bring up
要揭晓真正重要的成绩
the time that really matters.
赌了大价钱了
The one where a lot's at stake.
迈凯伦
The McLaren...
迈凯伦P1
The McLaren P1.
-你在紧张吗 -没有 -真的 -没有
- Are you nervous? Sure? - No. No.
-一点点都没有 -没有
- A little bit? - No!
我才没有紧张 -为什么要紧张
- I'm not nervous. - Why be nervous?
你可以拿一辆手推车或者类似的
You could get, like, a shopping trolley
装上你所有的东西
and keep all your things in it.
在桥底下交几个新朋友
Make some new friends under a bridge somewhere.
-哈蒙德 -我建议卖器官 但别那样
- Hammond. - I'd say sell your body but don't do that.
安静 让我们
Be quiet! Let's-
让我们把时间给P1 我们开始吧
Let's bring up the time of the P1. Here we go.
-哦天哪 -在哪儿
- Oh, God. - Where is it?
万岁
Yes!
这太逗了 因为你说过
That is funny. Because you said...
它是最快的 但它不是最快的
the fastest, but it's not the fastest.
它是最慢的
It's the slowest!
女士们先生们 记者 播音员
Ladies and gentlemen, journalist, broadcaster
无家可归的人 杰里米 克拉克森
and homeless man, Jeremy Clarkson.
这就是事实 这就是事实
That's what it is. That's what it is.
你们不会真的把我的房子拆了吧
You're not really going to knock my house down?
是的 我们会的
Yes, we are.
-愿赌服输 -都说定了
- A bet is a bet. - That's the deal.
而且我们会录下来 -但是有件事
- And we're going to film it. - No, but the thing is,
用迈凯伦自己的轮胎的话
on the tires that the McLaren can be bought with,
它是最快的
it was faster.
我们从刚开始就说好了
We agreed right at the start
我们都用一样的轮胎跑
we'd all run on the same tires.
那可是在你的车输掉前就定好的
That was the deal before your car lost.
所以让我们
So let's just...
让我们总结一下这第一集 好嘛
Let's just sum this first show up, shall we?
我失去了房子
I've lost my house.
我们和观众打了起来 -而且很惨烈
- We've had a fight with the audience. - Big one.
有个人把我们的无人机射了下来
Somebody shot our drone down.
而且我们杀了三个大名人
And we've killed three quite major celebrities.
是的 乐观点讲
Yeah, but on the plus side,
我保时捷是最快的
my Porsche was the fastest!
伴随着这个糟糕的失望之情
And on that terrible disappointment,
我想是结束的时候了
I'm afraid it's time to end.
十分感谢你们的到来
Thank you all very much for coming.
谢谢你们的收看
Thank you for watching.
下礼拜我们在约翰内斯堡再见
And we'll see you next week in Johannesburg.
再见
Good-bye!